You put me in a box. You told me to be sweet.
The stardust girl, the perfect V. You told me
soften up. You told me know your place
But you never saw the fire in my face Cause I'm not
your doll I'm not your pretty toy I'm not just a
picture for a poster boy I'm not your doll I'm
here to make a choice And I'm gonna make you hear
my voice Rise!
You're scared of the noise You're scared of the
grit You're terrified that I'm not gonna fit In
the tiny world you built for me But I'm about to
set myself free Cause I'm not your doll I'm not
your pretty toy I'm not just a picture for a
poster boy I'm not your doll I'm here to make a
choice And I'm gonna make you hear From my
heart.
You are the story to be told Well, I'm the one
who'll break the mold You want to start us, you
get the fire My voice is real and it's getting
higher
Cause I'm not your doll I'm not your pretty toy
I'm not just a picture for a poster boy I'm not
your doll I'm here to make a choice And I'm gonna
make you hear my voice
Not your doll
Hear my voice.